

CONTACT

+8801935654733
sohailarman@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/fai
sal-ahmed-86005127/

EDUCATION

Shaistaganj High School Habiganj, Bangladesh Secondary School Level

PERSONAL INFO

FAISAL AHMED
MARRIED
10-OCTOBER-1979
BANGLADESHI
MUSLIM

SKILLS

AUTOCAD, PHOTOSHOP, ILLUSTRATOR, WORD, EXCEL, SKETCHUP, 3D STUDIO MAX.
HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS, REACT.JS, C#, .NET FRAMEORK

FAISAL AHMED

AUTOCAD DRAFTSMAN

PROFILE

AutoCAD Draftsman with 16 years of experience in Electro-Mechanical Discipline. I am eager to learn and further my proficiencies by constantly improving my work. I am confident that I can measure up to the expectations of the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2021

JUNIOR DEVELOPER / SIYANA, BANGLADESH

Responsible for assisting with coding, testing, design adjustments, and client reviews with the supervision of senior developers.

2005 - 2018

CHIEF DRAFTSMAN / CEPCO, SAUDI ARABIA

Responsible for preparation, checking, reviewing, CAD file modification and rectification based on consultant's comments and actual field verification for electro-mechanical projects.

2004 - 2005

DRIVER CUM PURCHASER / SALCO, SAUDI ARABIA

Responsible for purchasing / buying materials, automobile parts and other purchasing errands as required by the superior.

OTHER SKILLS

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY:

BENGALI, ENGLISH, HINDI, URDU.

DRIVING LICENSE:

BANGLADESH (VALID), SAUDI ARABIA (VALID).